All right. Um
as we get started here, I just uh
want to address the Dave Merritt
situation quickly.
Um
and I'll leave it at that when I'm when
we're done with it, but
uh just for regards to his
family and the situation. So,
um
uh
we have been in touch with David.
We understand the situation.
We've looked into it and uh
we'll continue to
get um
you know, word back from
as I go through the investigation of it.
Um but uh
David's home with his family. So.
Uh
and then the other part of this would be
uh Derrick Johnson
uh going into um the Chiefs Hall of
Fame.
Uh
we're
very excited to have him a part of that.
Uh well deserved and um
just a quick shout out to him on that.
Other than that, we're going to talk
about the players.
And that's where we'll start with.
Um
Mecole Hardman
uh from LSU cornerback. We ended up
trading up for him.
We thought that was important. I I I
know a lot of the mock drafts and that
had him had us taking him at that spot,
the ninth spot.
Uh and then people above us we also knew
were interested in corners, so we felt
like we needed to go up and and snag
him.
Uh
very similar to what we did with
McDuffie
uh when you really look at it.
Um
and I think he'll come in and and
contribute uh but like all the guys,
they've got to earn their spot on the
team and
so on, but uh he'll definitely have an
opportunity to do that. And uh
he's a heck of a player, heck of a kid.
I think when you have a chance to talk
to him if you already haven't.
Um
he's a good kid.
Tremendous amount of energy. Great ball
skills. Great feet. Good size.
And um
and good speed on top of it, so.
And then
um
with the 20
uh ninth pick, we ended up taking uh
Peter Woods
from Clemson. This is a kid we had our
eye on right from the beginning.
Um he he's uh
defensive tackle. He's got great
athletic ability. I think when you watch
him
you know, his highlights, you'll see
that. Just uh
tremendous athlete whether it's in the
pass game or the run game.
Great feet. Great hands on with his
escape ability with his
with his hands on sheds.
Uh
and and he's also a great kid. So, both
these guys are are great kids and hard
workers and so on, so
I think they'll be nice additions to the
football team.
Well, that time's yours.
Coach, you mentioned uh in trading up
like you did [clears throat] with
McDuffie. Do you see some similarities
in the traits and the skill set that
Mecole has, too?
Yeah, so he's a little bit bigger.
Mecole is a little bit taller.
Um
but both of them are physical guys.
And uh you know, McDuffie proved that he
can do it at this level. This This kid's
coming in and he's got to do that part.
But their traits in [clears throat]
college look similar.
The quick feet.
The plant and drive. With eliminating
excess steps. Being able to play man
coverage, getting up on you and pressing
you.
Um
and ball skills.
Anyways. Andy, So, I guess yes. Matt.
I know you don't want to ask a rookie to
come in and be sort of a, you know,
vocal presence [clears throat] right
away, but I mean you you put strong
premium on that. How how much do you see
him as being that sort of guy that can
can
offer the leadership, but also fit that
way? Yeah, [clears throat] I think he'll
spend like most of his he will spend
most of his time just trying to get in
the starting lineup and going, you know,
working on the defense.
And what Spags is
uh
you know, demands of those guys, so I
think they'll be
and we've got other guys who can
do the leadership part, but he has that
ability, yes. He's
um
he's a good kid that has good leadership
ability. Well,
but you know, they're out there on
they're out there on an island away from
everybody by his own,
there's not a whole lot of leading.
They're just taking care of business out
there. Did you think particularly
excited to hear from you guys when if
you could
uh rehash the call with them? Uh
Yeah, you know, we just talked to him
the other day, too. So, I mean literally
two days ago.
On a Zoom call, so he uh
um
good kid, but we we've talked to him a
couple times at the combine, so uh
so
but he was he he was excited to hear
from us. Andy, when you go
when you go defense defense in the first
round, I just wonder if you could speak
to where your offense currently is. I
know you have picks left in this draft,
but just in general, where do you think
the offense is right now?
Yeah, so we'll see how everything works
out with that. Um but
um I I thought it was important that we
we addressed the defense. I mean, I
uh
you know, that's a
that's an important
important side of the ball.
Um as much as I love the offense, right?
But uh that's an important side of the
ball and
we had some vacancies there that
uh we needed to take care of. Did
you feel that going in
tonight or was that just the way that
felt?
No, that's the way we felt going into
it, yeah.
I mean, you know, we didn't we traded
our secondary kind of away there, so
um
it it was good to get
and we've got some young guys coming up
that are we think are good, but this
this will be a nice addition.
I know you were going to follow up on
that, but
I wouldn't [clears throat] be doing my
job if I didn't ask. Is
um
is Coach Merritt subjected to the
personal conduct
where the where he have to go on a leave
of absence according to the league?
I wouldn't be doing my job if I didn't
tell I'm done telling you not to that
I'm done answering, but you know, that's
all right.
Uh we're we're on it together, man.
You did your justice, I did my justice.
So. Coach, um when you guys had those
Zooms at the end,
you said just a couple days ago with
Mecole, is that like a
finishing interview? Does that seal the
deal? Did you did [clears throat]
anything in that Zoom that really kind
of solidified it for you?
No, I mean, what you can tell is we
we've put him through uh
on the interview uh
uh
two-fold scheme evaluation of what they
know. So, we're going to ask him about
what he did in college and show him tape
of that on the Zoom.
And then we're going to teach him
a couple of things we do
and have him spit it back to us.
And see his what kind of retention he
has.
And um
you know, and then the tape is the
you're looking at tape and
workouts and all that stuff other other
than that part. But so, it's part of the
evaluation.
His just happened to be late.
Now, he had a million of these things.
The kid did, so they
you had to you had to fit those in to
their to their schedules. So, between
the travel that he was making and then
um
the Zooms that he had,
we ended up just two days ago with it.
Andy, when it comes to with Spags, I'm
sure you had a lot of say with this and
just the fit [clears throat] with his
scheme. Just what was that evaluation
process like then? How do you identify
these two specific guys? Cuz kind of
like what you did with Willie Gay and
Willie Gay on a lot. How do you
particularly get these two guys in
there? Yeah, so um
this is where Brett comes in cuz he does
a phenomenal job of
um
including the coaches in the evaluation
part as part of it.
So, you get an idea
um
how the coaches feel that they'd fit in
the scheme. The scouts go out and gather
players and they they keep scheme in
mind,
but they're looking for good players in
general and they're good people and
citizens and all that stuff. So,
um
but the coaches look at these guys and
then they rank them.
And that's what Brett wants done. So,
they give them a ranking and then Brett
kind of fits it into his formula.
Um
of his guys and their evaluation, so
uh the coaches like both these guys.
Um Spags, you know, he he was big
big on the corner. He liked him a lot.
So,
it was Christmas for him. How's How's
How's his ability in the open field in
terms of tackling? It looks like he's a
very good physical player in press man
coverage, but
You know what, Andy? He was a wrestler.
He was a wrestler
growing up.
Dad threw him in when he was a kid and
wrestled all his way through. So, he's
kind of got that
he kind of knows how to get down there
and get dirty and um
but he did that does that well. Takes
good angles, which
you don't learn in wrestling, but you
you do
by playing. He does a nice job with
that. How does um he influence what you
can do, how how he may impact your
defensive front, and
the allure of being sort of an
understudy to Chris Jones?
Yeah. Um
two
two different size guys.
Um but both good athletes. So,
I I think that's what he gives he gives
you that quickness. Um
I I'm not
you can say Aaron Donald type quick.
Well,
he's not Aaron Donald yet, right? That's
a good challenge for him.
Uh but he has he has that ability inside
and you're seeing in the league now guys
that maybe aren't the biggest guys,
but they're extremely quick and have
great body control and can rush the
passer. Shortest distance to the
quarterback is are those dudes right in
there.
And so, he gives you a little bit of
that.
And we were looking for that.
So, and he's a great kid.
Coach, just talked to
Marcel on his own. Seems like he doesn't
lack confidence. Did you feel that way
when you talked to him? How beneficial
was that coming to you from? Yeah, you
know this, but you don't want corners
that don't have confidence.
>> [laughter]
>> If somebody's going to be cocky, you
want those guys to be cocky. But, he
he's a
he he's a he he's a confident guy.
Um
uh
he believes in himself, but there
there's a humble side to him, too, which
I appreciate.
You can get a little bit of that on
those Zooms Yeah. cuz we grill them.
And we we're not showing them all good
plays when he played. So, any of these
guys, we pull out a couple of their bad
ones
and show it to them. So, we're not there
to pump their egos up. We're there to
say "Hey,
what happened?"
So, and and some guys handle that good
and some don't. But, he handled it and
very up front with it. Yeah. I was
wrong. I should have done this. You
know,
you get a good feel for him on those.
So, he gave you the same energy
Great. Oh, yeah. Yeah, great energy.
Yeah. Have you guys talked to him? Yeah,
I'll be there.
>> Yeah. Yeah, he he I think that's what
what you're going to get. Anything
specific or anything you remember about
him sort of recapping or anything he
said that was particularly interesting
about one of those plays?
Yeah, I just I thought he
I thought he was humble with them.
That's uh probably the best
best thing I can tell you. He wasn't
[clears throat] afraid
the
there's certain there's guys that are
confident and
um
you know, then there are other ones that
are
Anyways, he he he was confident and but
he wasn't afraid to
be critiqued and he would come back with
a solution to the problem.
And in a humble way.
So, you didn't have that other edge that
as a coach, that's a tough thing to
break.
When you're when you're with guys, if
guys aren't coachable,
you're probably not going to be coaching
very long.
So.
Coach, who is this guy? Last two guys,
we'll go Todd and then we'll go Matt. Go
ahead, Todd.
Tornado warning during the draft, is
that the first for you? Well, we were
hoping you guys wouldn't show up.
>> [laughter]
>> What did that affect you guys
[clears throat] in the room? What did
you guys have to do?
Uh well, the draft room is right in the
middle of the building. It's actually
one of the tornado spots, uh
shelter spots, so
uh worked out well. We all just went in
there and
did our thing. Last one, Matt. I was
going to ask the same thing. So, I mean,
you know, you've been around long enough
for tornadoes, I guess. Yeah, sure. How
about a guy like yourself? No, Shurmur,
you know. It was like training camp when
the lightning strikes come. You know, we
all have to clear.
He was pacing the hallway. So,
he's got that
I think he he was watching out for you
guys.
All right, thanks, coach.
All right.
Thought of everything.
Yeah, exactly.
>> Mhm.
>> [clears throat]
>> All right, you guys ready?
Well, um super excited to add two new
members to the Chiefs Kingdom. Uh
ended up having a trade with Cleveland,
traded up
to six in exchange for 74 and 148 to
select Mansour Delaine. And then at 29,
we selected
defensive lineman Peter Woods from
Clemson. Um you know, really excited
about both prospects and you know, with
that we'll take your questions. Can you
go through the trade and what
Yeah.
Yeah, so obviously you put a
put a lot of time um into kind of just
um understanding the landscape and you
know,
give credit to Mark Richard and our uh
data analytics team.
We've done so many predictive models and
>> [clears throat]
>> almost every model that
you know, we ran, it kind of said that
you know, looking at the stack of
players,
you know, we figured obviously
Bailey and Reese would go and [snorts]
then when we got into that stack of you
know,
and we had identified Mansour Delaine
early on as a guy we wanted and it just
looked like the predicted model said
that you know, the Saints are going to
be the biggest obstacle. And so, you
know, when you kind of go through, I've
been doing this for a few years now and
um you know, you start the process off
where I mean Cleveland Cleveland made it
obvious early on that they're going to
be interested in trading. So, we had
some traction with Cleveland. And then
as the days went on,
um
you know, it was clear the Redskins
weren't going to do anything and
I know Mickey, if there's one guy that's
more aggressive than me, that's it's
Mickey and he you know, I've had that
experience where we're kind of eyeing
the same guy and when you try to call
them when they're on the pick, it just
it doesn't work out. So, um
when you looked at you know, their
roster, two years ago they lost Paul
Paulson Adebo to the Giants and then
just this past off season they lost
Adoree' Jackson. I mean, so they were
down two corners.
You know, we lost our number one and
number two corners and so,
you know, we just decided and we had
Mansour Delaine as a top five guy on our
board and we just made a decision that
if we got in striking distance, let's
just go up there and and not leave it to
chance. We felt it would come down to us
in New Orleans. You know, we thought
that there was a slight chance the
Redskins could go Delaine at seven. Um
we kind of had them pegged in for Tate.
And then when once uh once Tate left, um
you know, it just kind of solidified our
decision to go up there and if if you
want this guy, I've always said this,
you know, you do all this work and you
put all this time into this, but you
want a guy um
you know, you got to go go find a way to
get him and again, when you look at the
landscape, um
you know, it was funny cuz we kind of
had like when we're picking, it looks
like it'll be Tyson, Delaine, Downs kind
of in that stack and kept going through
it and you know, we just relied on our
data analytics and said like the Saints
would be likely to take Delaine there
just because they're losing the two
corners the last two years and again,
similar predicament. So, um just went up
there and and got that guy and it's
funny because
three, four weeks ago when we were going
through the 30 visits, um I bumped Steve
and I said we're going to bring bring
our corner and he's like, "Don't bring
him in. Just don't bring him in. Let's
just zoom him. Let's keep it quiet."
Thought we did a good job. I think a lot
of people thought we might go offensive
line there. Um but this was our guy uh
the whole time. You know, again,
assuming Bailey and Reese were off the
board, um great players, but I mean, we
had Delaine right up there and it's hard
to find, you know,
good corners and I know that we've done
well over the years of of addressing
corners late, but
you know, when you're kind of within
reach of a of a top corner, you know, we
did that a couple years ago. I think we
traded three and a four to get McDuffie.
So, you know, traded three and a five to
get um Mansour Delaine. So, we're
extremely excited. What what makes him
the guy?
>> [snorts]
>> No, it was that fine balance of
you know, being responsibly aggressive
and you know,
we really value that second round uh
first round pick, second first round
pick I should say. And you know, again,
we kind of had a threshold like, "Look,
we still need a lot on this team. We
have a lot of holes we have to cover,
you know, edge and D-line and corner and
some wide receiver depth and what have
you. Um and so like, "Look, if it makes
sense to do something, um want to really
keep one don't want to touch, you know,
129 or or 40 is it 40 tomorrow we have
yet? Don't want to touch those. Want to
keep those, but look, if we get
if [snorts and clears throat] we get to
Cleveland and I mean, we kind of
you know, doing those mocks, I mean, we
kind of
think we had Styles probably going there
and Tate went, you know, with the flip
of those guys, maybe Reese and Styles,
but I think we all kind of knew the
first five and
Tate was a little bit
um of a curveball, but I mean, it wasn't
I mean, it was a good pick.
Um but
you know, we said if we get in this
window, we can get a top five guy on our
board, let's just go get him. And again,
then you know,
with Tate going,
we felt like he could be in play for the
Redskins, but you know, we were really
doing our work on the Saints and like I
said, you know, the that that team
losing two corners in the last two years
and us losing two corners in one off
season,
um it's just how we got our guy. What
what makes Mansour the guy?
Uh you know, listen, he
he's super fluid, he's athletic, You
know, obviously ran that 4-3, but he's a
guy that that plays patient,
is super aware, has great ball skills.
He'll He's tough, he'll tackle.
We think he can play inside and outside.
Again, just you know, we feel like he
was the most complete corner and I'm
sure he was the consensus number one
corner. And again, when you're picking
at nine and and you're right there and
you can get the number one corner in the
draft,
you just go get him, but I mean we think
he has you know, the full package. He
was a former wrestler growing up.
He'll tackle. That's a big deal for
Steve, as you know, but
Stacy, but also that position
flexibility. We think he can go inside
and outside and give us
you know, a lot of flexibility. So now,
you know, we have
a guy and Noah Williams that did some
great things for us last year and you
know, I think Christian Fulton showed
what he can do when he's when he's
healthy, but I mean I mean that was
super high on our priority list to knock
that corner position out. And
so we just decided to go do it early.
Brad, Steve is so important [snorts] in
these conversations. Fitness is so
important. What did Steve say about
Mansour when you were talking? Yeah, I
mean it was yeah. I'm not so sure Steve
wouldn't have taken him over anybody. So
you know, I told Steve I said, well,
you know, we'll have a chance I think,
you know, because he'll get to six and
then you know, and I don't think he'll
be the sixth pick, but
he'll probably go if not seven, you
know, we felt like eight was the spot.
So
as I mentioned, you know, Steve
had me cancel the 30 visits just to
I think if you guys heard the call I
said to him, I said you didn't hear from
a lot from us and that was by intent,
you know, I mean when you're sitting
there at nine and again, I've said this
earlier when you know, you lose your
starting corners and then the Saints
lost one the year before and one this
year. I mean you're looking at a team
that probably has the same needs and and
look the Saints got a good great player
and
he could have been in consideration. We
just felt it was a huge priority for us
to knock that corner position out. Brad,
it was a little unusual for us to watch
the draft with the [snorts] eight-minute
thing and it was a little weird on what
was going on. Did you guys make the
trade? Did you already know that Reese
was in for the Giants when you made the
trade? What was the true timing?
Um well, I had I had talked to
Cleveland. I mean shoot, I talked to
Andrew at the owners meeting and he kind
of put it on our radar that you know, we
um
they would have interest and you know, I
kind of took that back with the group
and you know, that's when the research
you know, we just spent all the time
just kind of analyzing the teams and and
what they would do. You would obviously
don't want to trade picks if you can sit
there and get a guy.
And that's where I mean we just
exhausted our resources into just you
know, what are these teams going to do?
And you never know. It's not it's an
inexact science, but again, all of our
you know, predictive models said that
there was you know, when they had the
the graphs and the charts that again
Mark sent to me, it was you know, the
most likely player the Saints would
select would would be Dean. And and
again, I'm not speaking on behalf of of
New Orleans. They they selected a great
player and and maybe they would have
taken him, right? But
you know, we also
have [snorts] a process and we go
through that and we trust it and you
know, if we feel that we don't want to
lose a guy by what our predictive models
are saying, let's just go up there and
and get the guy. You mentioned that
there was a zoom that he had with his
staff very instrumental. When did you
guys decide that this was the guy? Was
it a month ago or It was yeah, it was a
little bit ago. I mean we know we kind
of when you're going through this,
you're you know that you know, the
Baileys and the Reeses and you know,
obviously Mendoza and Love. I mean let's
just you know, nothing's for sure
certain, but I mean I think we're all
pretty safe to say those guys were going
to be gone. So then we start looking up
at the pool of players and looking at
the teams ahead of us and
and then also knowing that you know, the
the Giants would probably go defense,
but you know, maybe a Styles, maybe a
Downs, maybe you know,
but we also the bit of information we
had was that Cleveland was going to
trade,
right? And and then I as the weeks go
on, you realize that Washington won't.
And again, I know Mickey and I I know
that you know, he's he's going to pick a
guy and
so it's like, well,
it's either go to six and get Dean, the
guy you want, the guy that we have a top
five guy on our board or just leave it
to chance and just you know, if
the Saints go wide out, you know, we go
corner. Sure we had the same names on
the board, but I think
man, I would say at least three or four
weeks ago. I mean we kind of just honed
in on this guy and he was our guy and
you know,
whatever everyone think we're going to
go off off this line.
You got another guy. You got another guy
tonight. What tell Yeah. Yeah, tell us
what led into that. Yeah, I mean we just
you know, you guys have seen it across
the the league just the the depth of
defensive lines is so important. You
look at obviously what Seattle did and
and and New England and those teams. I
mean they just have a plethora of
defensive linemen across the board and
you know, what we like about Peters is
he's you know, he's a versatile guy. He
has strength and power, but he's also
athletic and has some pass rush and and
look he's one of the younger guys in the
draft. I think he just turned 21.
Super big upside with him and
again, I think it's a priority for us
more than anything is you know,
obviously you guys know we
have invested on the offensive line over
the years and you know, that old
blueprint O line D line and and then
work from the corner receiver and all
that, but
we've done that with the O line and you
know, we're going to continue to do that
with the D line now and we just want to
add numbers and and talent across the
board and you know, get Omar coming back
now and now you have Peter Woods and now
you have Chris Jones and now you have
Tonga. It looks a lot different than it
did last year already and you know, we
still have some more picks to go and
hopefully we can keep adding. Brad, you
guys have been very successful in
developing young corners. How much did
that go into this pick? Yeah, well,
you know,
I think that on on one end, you know, we
do a great job of um
you know, just the communication of of
you know,
we do a good job of I've always said
this like
the way we do things here is you know,
we go through all the players and and
the guys we like, we only give our
coaches the guys we like. We don't give
them everybody. We just give them the
small pockets of players. Pocket of
player one, pocket of player two and
and you know, it cuts down the numbers
for the coaches and it makes their
reports you know, more accurate for us,
but
um I think that's
why we've had success later on in the
draft, but
you know, when you have a guy like
Mansour's Dean skill set, you don't find
that late in the draft and and again,
we're sitting right there. Let's just
just go get him, but I just think that
you know, our success in developing and
and
turning out corners has a lot to do with
the communication and trust and
you know, we see a guy, you know, we go
get him and we've identified the skill
traits that skill sets that work for us
and
like I said, I mean um
Steve was obviously, you know, we had to
make some tough organizational decisions
with trading Trent and then we lost
Jaylen and
um
but he's a happy camper today. You know,
he's he's super fired up and this was
you know, I'm glad that you know,
we were excited about a guy and you
know, Steve was excited about a guy and
glad we were able to get him one cuz we
lost three of them, right? With Cook
too, the safety. So it was it was big
for us. Brad, where where is Omar right
now as far as
health and what do you expect from him
in the next Yeah, I think you know,
again
you guys know how to roll. I don't want
to speak for Rick, but I I
totally expect him ready to go for
training camp. I think you'll see him
out there at OTAs and you know, exactly
at what point he'll be just full go at
that those OTAs, we'll see, but I mean
certainly think that you know, he'll be
ready to rock and roll for for Saint Joe
and I think he'll do a lot at the OTA. I
don't know if um you know, we'll take
the red jersey jersey off him. You know,
we probably will like let that slowly
happen and let him kind of acclimate and
ease his way into this, but
certainly expect to have him for the
start of training camp. Brad, you
I had this like a week ago about just
the comparisons of the 22 draft having
two first rounders.
You guys went corner and defensive line
yet again. Just do you see the
similarities of what
Mansour and and Peter can do similar
from a character standpoint and more so
than even just on the field of being
able to contribute early on?
Yeah, I mean you know, I didn't
I didn't even think about that, but like
in 22, we you know, we I did think of
the trade, right? So we moved to three
and four I think to get McDuffie, moved
to three and 105 here to get Dean added
George and and now we add another
interior defensive lineman, but
I mean those guys were impact players
right out of the gate and and we expect
these guys to be impact players right
out of the gate. I mean that was one of
the things too. I There's a lot of guys
out there that we think have a bright
future, but you know, we're kind of in
that we want to get younger and we want
to get deeper, but we also you know, we
don't want to redshirt guys and have
these guys kind of just you know, we
want these guys we've identified two
guys that we think can come in right
away and and help us. Just McDuffie
trade up that you talked about a couple
times. Did that make it easier to move
up for Mansour in this particular
scenario? Um
>> [snorts]
>> Yeah, I I
I think it does. I I think we just you
know, again, we just
trust the board and and whether it be a
Trent McDuffie or or if it was a
different player. I mean if you know, we
have a chance to get one of those guys
that we feel are are true difference
makers, you know, we go up there and and
get it done, but
and look we've again, we've had success
developing corners, but this is a
different skill set here. This is really
unique and
we'll have an opportunity to add a young
guy that we think we can grow and
develop and you know, some of those guys
have done that, but you know, we think
you know, Mansour's a little bit of a
different type of player where you know,
again, I'm sure [clears throat] it was
the consensus number one corner across
the board. So
should be able to come out and help us
right away. We're going to last couple
topics. Go ahead.
Not on the football field, but we had a
tornado warning I guess. Was that
interesting in the draft room?
>> Yeah.
Well, I Brian Schaffer came in and had
mentioned we all had to go into the
>> [clears throat]
>> I I move a lot. I don't like I don't
really like staying in the draft room. I
actually like going to my office and
letting the picks come off and just kind
of think. And then when you go in
there's a ton of people and just like
being by myself, but he had come in and
said that there's a tornado warning and
we actually all have to go into the
draft room.
And I said, look, there ain't nothing
blowing this building down. I mean this
thing is like complete concrete here.
We're going to be all right, I said. So,
but it was a little different.
But yeah, we certainly
followed all the safety protocol, for
sure.
Last one, Sam. Without revealing what
your board looks like for tomorrow, just
wondering if
how you perceive maybe the the first 10
picks shaking out.
Yeah, I mean, we'll
go up there and I'll go up there now and
and huddle up with my staff, but I mean,
you know, I think you guys kind of know
the direction we're in. I mean, we're
going to continue to add to the
defensive line and if we can
you know, get some some more edge help,
for sure. But I mean, you know, again,
we're not going to shy away from
offensive line and defensive line and
there's some talented receivers on the
board. So,
um
it's
you know, I don't like being in this
position. Hopefully, we're not in this
position again, but
um
it is a lot better to come back tomorrow
and be picking right out of the gate
again. I mean, we typically used to
waiting and seeing a handful of guys
that we know are never going to be
there. So, this is a little bit more
exciting for us
and it happens it happened fast. I mean,
I I don't know if you guys felt the same
way, but I mean, tonight flew by. So,
tomorrow will be even quicker. So,
spent a lot of time tonight and then
we'll huddle up again tomorrow and kind
of put our board together and we'll have
eight names and, you know, hopefully add
another talented player to our roster.
Was that just baiting us to think
offensive line? Oh, no.
>> [laughter]
>> It's all on the table now. I just, you
know, but um
yeah. Yep. All right, thanks, guys. Yep.